absolutvision.com 2007-12-29

# AbsolutVision Royalty Free Stock Photo Gallery

### [Gallery](http://www.absolutvision.com/index.php) | Privacy policy

The following forms are provided without warranty of any kind, express or implied, and the author and publisher specifically disclaim any and all such warranties, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, where permissible, and any and all liability arising directly or indirectly from any use whatsoever of the form agreement. As with any form, these forms cannot appropriately be applied to a specific transaction without first being substantively revised; therefore, it should not be used as a replacement for professional legal, tax, financial, and technical advice in any transaction.

#### WEB SITE PRIVACY STATEMENT

AbsolutVision has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. Due to the sensitive nature of the information we collect from our users, we believe it is important to satisfy strict privacy requirements. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:

#### COLLECTED INFORMATION

The following section describes the information we collect from you and indicates the primary purposes why we collect each type of information from you. If we use your information or disclose or distribute your information to third parties for a purpose that is not related to the following purposes, we will notify you by email of your right to opt-out of that use, disclosure or distribution beforehand. Your right to opt-out shall be governed by the Choice/Opt-Out Section below.  
As described below in more detail, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is or may be used to help identify you, to track activity within our site and to gather broad demographic information. Our Web server will collect IP information.  
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your session ID. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.  
Our site's registration and order form requires users to give us contact information (such as name and email address) and financial information (such as account or credit card numbers). The user's contact information is used to contact the user when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings as set forth in the Choice/Opt-Out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration and to bill the user for products and services.  
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our Web site. We use this data to tailor the user's experience at our Web site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.  
The demographic information may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Aggregate basis means that your information will be generalized with the data we collect from all our users. For example, we may share the average age or income level of our users with advertisers. We will not share personally identifiable information, such as contact information, unique identifiers, financial information and demographic information, with advertisers about any particular individual that uses our Web site.  
AbsolutVision may also use the information we collect from you to optimize our Web site so that it is more beneficial to users like yourself and to us. This site contains links to other sites. AbsolutVision is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### SECURITY

This Web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All user data is stored on our servers.  
The user may request, via email, additional information about AbsolutVision's security practices. The requested security information will be made available to the user via email, fax or postal mail, in our discretion.

#### DATA ACCESS & ACCURACY

AbsolutVision is not responsible for inaccuracies in data provided by third parties, such as credit reporting bureaus. If you would like to update or correct your contact information, please contact us at [subscribe@absolutvision.com](mailto:subscribe@absolutvision.com).

#### CHOICE / OPT-OUT

Our Web site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Absolutvision at the point where we request information about the user. You can send email at unsubscribe@absolutvision.com for removing your information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

#### CHANGE IN CONTROL

If we experience a ''change in control'' (defined below), we may amend our information practices as described in this privacy statement. We will post on our Web site's home page a notice or a link to a notice which will describe how we will amend our privacy statement. If you do not agree to our amended privacy statement, you may contact us as described in this privacy statement and we will allow you to opt out of the proposed amendments to our privacy statement with respect to the information that we have previously collected from you. ''Change in control'' means any of the following events:  
\- we undergo a reorganization, merger, consolidation, acquisition or other restructuring involving all or substantially all of our voting securities and/or assets, by operation of law or otherwise;  
\- we become insolvent;  
\- we make a general assignment for the benefit of creditors;  
\- we suffer or permit an appointment of a receiver for our business or assets;  
\- we becomes subject to any proceedings under any bankruptcy or insolvency law, whether domestic or foreign; or  
\- we are liquidated, voluntarily or otherwise.

#### CONTACTING THE WEB SITE

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [policy@absolutvision.com](mailto:policy@absolutvision.com).
